
1. Provide one login page that will allow users to log onto and use the web site. Users who cannot login, or who have logged out should not be able to access any page except the login page.  - login.php / loginFail.php / logout.php

2. Another page of the website should allow you to insert a new customer's details into the customers table using an HTML5 form to gather the customer data and PHP to connect to the MySQL database and insert the values.  - register.php 
3. One page of your website should link to the activities table in your MySQL database using PHP and the contents of the activities table should be listed on the page in a suitable format. All customers should be able to book activities from this page. - activities.php / activities2.php 
4. All customers should be able to see their booked_activities table. From the booked activities table customers should be able to navigate to activities to see activity details.  - bookedActivities.php 
5. Another page should allow a user to search for an activity and display the results that match the search criteria. A basic search containing a single searchable field will achieve the pass mark for this section. More marks can be gained for more advanced searching such as combining two search fields together using AND/OR logic.  - search.php 
6. An academic security report web page of 1000 words or fewer that critically reviews the site security measures, including features that could be added. This page requires academic journal and paper references and should be linked to the home page. References are excluded from the word count  - report.html 
7. An appropriately designed homepage/index page.  - homepage.php / nav.php
8. OpenWeatherAPI - footer.php / main.js
9. Session start - header.php
10. Styling - stylesheet.css 
